[
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "question": "All program codes have to be compiled into an executable file in order to be run. This file can then be executed on any machine.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In World of Warcraft lore, Thrall is the original wielder of 'Doomhammer'.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Muse is a British (English) rock band",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Science: Mathematics",
        "question": "L'H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "Seoul is the capital of North Korea.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "'Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.' is a grammatically correct sentence.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "Sean Connery wasn't in 'Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull' because he found retirement too enjoyable.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]